You may notice that I'm a lot more
relaxed during this video.
My voice is very, very relaxed because I
actually got to play around with this
thing a little bit and I feel just much
more
peaceful and calm from it.
We're going to be looking at the Naipo
Shiatsu Pillow Massager with heat. And
this is for your back and your neck or
even your legs or anything else like
that as well. So, let's dive in. Let's
open it up, see what's inside, and then
you can see it in action.
All right, we have instruction manual,
the actual massaging pillow,
and the two power adapters also. Cool
thing about this is we get actually a
car adapter so you can attach it to your
seat. Whether or not that's safe, I
don't know, but
I'm definitely going to try it.
All right. We also have the wall
adapter. We're going to be testing it
through this because
I give power to it and that's about it.
So, uh basic one. It's a pretty lengthy
cable, too. I mean, this cable's pretty
long. I think it's like
maybe 5 ft, almost 6 ft. So, it'll give
us some good distance as well and I
happen to bring this little extension
cord as well. We're going to plug it in.
And we will plug it in to see this thing
in action. I'm diving right in because
this thing will speak for itself once
you see it moving.
Uh we have this nice band that can also
go around a chair or something. I
wrapped it around my computer chair. It
fits perfectly. The band holds it nicely
in place as well.
Another cool thing to notice is that
when you plug it in, it plugs in, but
then you heard that pop. This actually
pops into place so in case it gets
stretched, it's going to give a little
bit of resistance before becoming
unplugged. It's a nice little design
feature in this that is worth noting.
All right, we have our on-off button
over here.
All right, I press and hold it
and it turns it on.
Uh according to the manual, it starts
about 20 minutes of just, you know, the
heat and massage therapy. And then after
that, it turns off the heat and still
massages. So, it's going to keep
cycling, I would assume. I didn't use it
for 40 minutes. I used it for about 15
minutes, maybe tops. But, it's nice. Uh
these arms are really Are these arms or
knobs, I guess you could call them, are
They're really good. They slide nice and
smooth inside this mesh cover. Um you
know, the heat is nice. It's not too
hot. It's just a nice level of a little
bit of warmth. And with winter coming, I
hold it I love it.
So, it goes it goes. Eventually, it
stops for a second, and then it will
reverse direction going the opposite
way.
Uh
this thing is awesome. So,
I enjoyed it. I'm probably going to be
writing up my blog post about this as
well, and probably doing the editing and
everything else associated with these
videos while this thing is actually
working on my back because it feels
awesome.
It's just the right amount of pressure.
You can increase your back pressure on
it. There's the reverse.
Um and it won't give in. Like, the motor
won't stop. I mean, it will slow if I
try to slow it down, but it always finds
a way to slip through at the end. So, uh
it's nice. It's good quality, and you
know, it's a pretty inexpensive device
as well. Great gift for somebody who's
got a lot of back problems or a lot of
stress in their life, and uh
it's great to buy yourself, too. So, you
know, when the holidays come around,
treat yourself. If you like this, I'll
leave a link in the video in the
description of the video. And if you
have any comments or questions or
anything, please leave them. All right.
Thanks for watching.